(前情提要)
有人出价要买我的公寓
I got an offer on my place.
(最佳与最终出价)
我们可以重新开始 寻找我们夫妻的风格
We could start over, find our style as a couple.
如果我搬走 我在新家会快乐吗
If I move, how do I know I'll be happy there?
看来我们的母亲有些共通点
Sounds like our mothers had a few things in common.
- 多说一点 - 这么说吧 她伤我很深
- Tell me more. - Let's just say she did a number on me.
我先生在亚柯尼亚做过一些生意
而莱斯特曾经替他工作
My husband ran a few businesses in the Arconia, and Lester worked for him.
莱斯特不想明说他做的事
Lester didn't wanna tell me much about what he did.
他不是很喜欢那份工作
He didn't feel good about the job.
但你们认为有人杀了我丈夫
But you think somebody killed my husband?
- 可以请你吃晚餐吗 - 我没有证据
- Could I take you out to dinner? - I have no evidence
显示你其实是好人
that you're actually a good guy.
我们其实只是一群有钱人 在争论打赌的事
We're just a bunch of rich people hashing out a bet.
就是我们上次在赌场想解决的问题
The same one we were trying to settle the last time we were in that gaming parlor.
你们门房死的那晚 我们赌了一笔很大的合约
The night your doorman died, we played for a very big contract.
你们当中有人想盖纽约市第一间赌场
One of you is planning to build New York City's first casino.
我想我会先开始翻修奥利佛的公寓
I think I'll start renovations with... Oliver's apartment.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你收到的出价是我的
That offer on your place was from me.
(卡蜜拉俱乐部)
是我要买下这里所有的公寓
I'm the one buying up all the apartments here.
你要把亚柯尼亚大楼变成赌场
You're turning The Arconia into a casino? All in.
数千年来 男人都将运气比喻为女性
For thousands of years, men have sung about luck being a lady.
在《布兰诗歌》中
卡尔奥福对幸运女神深深着迷
In Carmina Burana, Carl Orff obsesses over Fortuna, the goddess of fortune.
法兰克辛纳屈祈求运气能当个淑女
Frank Sinatra prayed for luck to be a lady,
却还是担心她会「对别人的骰子吹气」
but still worried she'd go "blow on some other guy's dice."
男人喜欢把生命中
无法控制的事与厄运都归咎于
Men love to blame anything in their life that they can't control... their bad luck,
女人
on ladies.
你们这些禽兽听着 下一轮我请客
Listen, you animals, next round is on me, alright?
只要这瓶苏格兰威士忌还没老到
能跟人亲热或入伍
As long as the scotch isn't old enough to be kissed, or drafted.
(两年前)
糟了
Uh-oh
装潢女王注意到我的破皮革
Queen of Decor has noticed my cracked leather.
我人生的谷底
Worst day of my life.
更有个性了
Adds character.
你真会说话
You're just being sweet.
这个地方曾经风光过 滚开
Ah, this place has seen better days. Hey, get lost.
我知道她喜欢什么
I know what she likes.
想来场大改造吗
Interested in a makeover?
- 你觉得呢 浏海
还是狼尾头 - 我是指赌场 傻瓜
- What are you thinking? Uh, bangs or a shag? - For the casino, you goof.
我可以帮忙提供女性的点缀
I could help. Give it a woman's touch.
这个点子如何
Ooh, what about this idea?
你让我一个月在这里 办一次私人的淑女之夜
Let me host a private Ladies' Night in here. Once a month.
一个没有雪茄 或大嗓门的男人来搭讪的夜晚
A night without cigars... or loud men hitting on us.
成交 我爱淑女
Done. I love ladies.
但别担心 除非她们有兴趣
否则我绝不会乱搭讪
But don't worry, I never hit on 'em unless they want me to.
- 如果她们有兴趣呢 - 那我就帮她们调酒
- And if they want you to? - Well, then, I make 'em a drink.
我们得因为一间赌场而搬走
We have to move out because of a casino?!
你记得我为了保住公寓做出什么事吗
Do you remember what I had to do to hold onto my apartment?
我烧了一个人
I burned a man.
我放火烧了一个好朋友 还买了一辆健身车
I set fire to a dear friend! Plus, I bought a Peloton.
你们好
- Hey! - Hi!
看看这个可爱的地方
Look at this cute place.
天啊 是THē Oh my gosh, THē!
我在上有氧舞蹈课
Oh, I'm taking a dance cardio class,
我们会用你的歌来搭配动作
and we're using one of your songs for a routine.
我很想示范 但有太多臀部动作了
I would show it to you, but it's got a lot of thrusting.
- 不适合淑女 - 没这个必要
- It's not appropriate for a lady. - Unnecessary.
梅宝贝 我的新老朋友
Mabitita, my new old friend,
我帮你弄到今晚派对的门票
I got you and however many plus-ones you want
你想带多少人都行
tickets to a party tonight.
我很想去 但我们都知道我会喝醉
I'd totally come with, but we both know I'd just get drunk,
and tomorrow I'm in a music video where I have to operate heavy machinery, so...
明天我要拍音乐录影带 和操作重型机械 所以
太感谢你了 我只是...有很多事要调查
Thank you so much. I just-- I have a lot of case stuff.
不 女孩 这跟调查有关 这是不可能收到的邀请
No, chica, this is case stuff. It's an impossible invite to get.
是为我这种重要女性举办的淑女之夜
It's a Ladies' Night for important ladies like moi,
而且就在大楼里
and it's literally in the building.
要从衣柜之类的地方进场
You get in through like-- like a closet or something,
有点像地下酒吧 不得了
sort of like a speakeasy. Ooh-la-la.
什么 尼奇死了耶 等等 派对是谁办的
What? But Nicky's dead. Wait, who's throwing this party?